{
    "id": "654b7de323fc49c7a0ebe2720c7f667d",
    "title": "No And Not",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………… all birds can sing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "No",
                "Not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a647e77cf04846a0856aa6d4f48977ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can meet you today, but ………………….. on Monday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "no",
                "not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eab0cc80422e444e8e2dc8e471a74e38"
        },
        {
            "question": "I sent her several letters, but received …………….. reply.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "no",
                "not"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9cf91c20b44c43e8a94840427c3e5799"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is a …………………. parking area.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "no",
                "not"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fc45509ada0f4cada8d46f9c62bfacc8"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is certainly ………………….. the most talented person in the team.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "no",
                "not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "16f607ad10da479bb561f5c79e2d5d19"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was …………………. at all amused.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "no",
                "not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ddf2daed2cf748b9b9aa89b6fe713935"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has ………………… children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "no",
                "not"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4559cc5a72b7490ca6d4a6f478b59418"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. two people are alike.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Not",
                "No"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "918fbd2baa884170b99e400a6e9fcd03"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… surprisingly, he failed the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "No",
                "Not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bdad2a25464748adb15484d98becd224"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was ………………… much we could do to help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "no",
                "not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c365972a14f74fbca18c8c83e18e4989"
        }
    ]
}